<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<soft>

    <res>
        <url>https://getsocietypress.org</url>
        <name>SocietyPress</name>
        <softname>societypress</softname>
        <cat>Portal/CMS</cat>
        <ver>0.51d</ver>
        <ver_min_498>6.0</ver_min_498>
        <desc>A free, open-source membership management platform built specifically for genealogical and historical societies. Manage members, events, a research library, genealogical records, newsletters, volunteers, a store, and more — all in one place. Built on WordPress.</desc>
        <features>
            <feature>Membership management with tiers, renewals, and self-service portal</feature>
            <feature>Event calendar with registration, waitlists, and Stripe/PayPal payments</feature>
            <feature>Research library with OPAC-style catalog and Open Library covers</feature>
            <feature>Genealogical record collections with GENRECORD and GEDCOM import/export</feature>
            <feature>Newsletter archive with PDF upload and automatic cover thumbnails</feature>
            <feature>Volunteer management with opportunities, signups, and hours tracking</feature>
            <feature>Online store with Stripe checkout</feature>
            <feature>Secure online voting and elections</feature>
            <feature>Page builder with 21 widget types</feature>
            <feature>5 pre-built child themes plus custom theme builder</feature>
            <feature>Automated backups with scheduling and rotation</feature>
            <feature>Role-based access control with 10 access areas and 8 role templates</feature>
            <feature>13 toggleable feature modules</feature>
        </features>
        <demo>https://demo.getsocietypress.org</demo>
        <support>https://getsocietypress.org/feedback/</support>
        <ratings>https://github.com/societypress/SocietyPress</ratings>
        <space>104857600</space><!-- 100 MB -->
        <type>php</type>
        <lang>
            <en>
                <admin_username>Admin Username</admin_username>
                <admin_pass>Admin Password</admin_pass>
                <admin_email>Admin Email</admin_email>
                <site_name>Site Title</site_name>
                <org_name>Organization Name</org_name>
                <org_email>Organization Email</org_email>
                <install_heading>SocietyPress Installation</install_heading>
                <install_desc>Set up your society's website. After installation, you'll be able to log in and start adding members, events, and content right away.</install_desc>
                <admin_heading>Administrator Account</admin_heading>
                <admin_desc>This is the login for the site administrator — typically the webmaster or board member who manages the website.</admin_desc>
                <org_heading>Society Information</org_heading>
                <org_desc>Basic information about your genealogical or historical society.</org_desc>
            </en>
        </lang>
    </res>

</soft>
